

Hanna A. Slivankova

Front-end developer (React)

💌 annslivankova@gmail.com 📞 +375259924552 👂 Minsk, Belarus

🛗 21/12/1991 🕏 https://annaslivankova.github.io/my_portfolio/

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/anna-slivankova-ba969a156/

🗘 https://github.com/AnnaSlivankova 🛭 🕲 @vinnis_2010

PROFILE

Hello, I am a person who has a strong passion for programming. I have experience in creating SPA with React/Redux(RTK)/TypeScript. Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies.

I'm planning to study Node.js because my next focus is to become a Full-Stack Developer. And also I have an interest in boosting my English to C1 level. I spend my leisure time on Codewars or speaking with native English speakers. Open to your suggestions.

SKILLS

React, Next js
Redux, RTK, RTK query

AXIOS, REST API
HTML5, CSS3

Unit Tests, StoryBook
Git

JavaScript, TypeScript

 Material UI, SASS, Styledcomponents

• English - C

EDUCATION

2022 – 2023 Front-End Developer

Minsk, Belarus IT-Incubator

2019 - presentMaster of Arts - MA, TheologyVienna, AustriaTCM International Institute

2011 – 2014 **Bachelor Degree - Economics**Minsk, Belarus International University 'MITSO'

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

03/2023 – present Minsk, Belarus part-time

Front-End Developer

React development using redux, react-redux, react-router-dom, reduxthunk, axios,

formik, ant-design libraries. Work with Hooks, TypeScript.

Refactoring, bug fixing, registration and login form creation.

Reusable components development.

2014 – 2022 Minsk, Belarus **UE** Belpromproject

Lead Economist

Execution and maintenance of contracts and various types of

agreements, including NDAs.

Communication with suppliers and customers.

Calculation of the cost of design work in accordance with the provided

drawings.

Conducting tenders for the development of project documentation for

construction.